Your long awaited friend
has returned today.
Go sit.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Can I see your backpack?
Why?
It won't take long.
I don't think so.
- I need to check your backpack.
- What are you doing?
And one more thing.
Then the three of you
went to see a show?
Yes.
And then?
I went straight home.
Straight home?
Straight home...
I didn't do it.
What?
I didn't do what you think I did.
What time roughly was that?
- Have some coffee.
- Thank you.
I don't know what time.
It was before midnight.
This isn't to scold or to lecture you.
I just want you to tell
me what really happened.
Did you two had a fight?
Did Kyung Min acted strangely?
or did she confide something to you?
According to the other girls,
you were the last one to see her.
The police will be here
to ask you some questions.
Kyung Min's missing.
AFTER MY DEATH
You must be going somewhere nice.
This is the latest model.
It's entirely a fire-retardant tent.
Just you and your husband can set it up.
You'll all fit even
if you have three kids.
Do you have anything bigger?
You must be going on a picnic.
I said I'd take care of it.
What's wrong with you?
This isn't sold elsewhere.
Everyone will really like it.
Thank you.
- All clear.
- Yes, okay.
Yes. It'll take 30-40 minutes.
Okay. See you later.
Hey! What the fuck!
Can't you drive properly?
Your driving sucks.
Hey. Lighter.
Shit.
In position.
- Hey, slow down.
- Farther left.
The backpack was found here.
This is frustrating.
Farther left.
Left! Left!
Pull it back up and lower it here.
Farther this way.
We dropped a dummy of
your daughter's weight
where her backpack was found.
It will show where the currents
might have taken your daughter.
We will search the area
starting from the bank there.
I hope we don't find her here,
but our goal is to find
her as soon as possible.
I'm sure some of you already know...
Lee Kyung Min, a student in class,
her backpack and shoes
were found yesterday
on the bridge out front.
She got good grades and
her parents have good jobs,
so why did she do it?
Perhaps it was
college entrance stress.
We recently divided
the students by GPA
and supervised the
upper-tier students separately.
- The pressure to keep her grade up...
- How does that make us look?
Can't you give a more
acceptable explanation?
Excuse me.
May I say something?
Go ahead.
First, I feel very responsible
as her homeroom teacher.
Such an impulse usually
stems from a mental illness.
She was an exceptional student,
so she might've had trouble
communicating with others,
and only listened to dark music,
which aggravates her illness.
So because she was so talented
and so exceptional,
she had trouble communicating
with her classmates
and felt very lonely.
Did she suffer from depression
or anything like that?
Well... She was in
my class last year,
and she did have a
very dark side of her.
Right, Mr. Seo?
Yes. I can't say she didn't.
She was listening to music
the entire class one time,
so I confiscated her phone to
see what she was listening to.
It was 90s North European music.
Do you want to listen to it?
Music that kids listen to these
days doesn't sound like music.
Go ahead.
- Is this on?
- Yes.
Maybe it's too late already.
Of course.
They're looking for her body now.
My friend said she saw her
last night on the bridge.
What, really? Damn.
It's really dark there.
I got cramps.
You talked to Mr. Seo this morning?
Yeah.
What did he say?
Nothing.
I said I didn't know anything.
I'm gonna lie down for a bit.
You were here all day,
not too long ago.
I don't think it's been a month.
Are you sure?
This is the last footage of her.
Who is she?
She's Lee Young Hee,
one of my students.
There's a CCTV in the
middle of the bridge.
Can I use this?
That CCTV is broken so we
can't verify her last location.
This is the school.
It's about 10 minutes away.
- And this...
- It's exactly 15 minutes away.
After 30 minutes, the other girl came out
from the other underpass which is 2 km away.
We checked the other CCTVs in
the area 4 hours before and after,
but there was no one suspicious
who might have hurt her.
Someone could have been
hiding, but we found no one.
So she probably jumped after
sending this student off.
Now that I think about,
she didn't socialize that much.
She didn't listen to K-pop.
We had nothing in common.
I think she liked very offbeat things.
I used to borrow Kyung Min's notes.
I was actually supposed to
return her notebook today.
And I don't think she was
particularly close to anyone.
She got along well
with everyone.
Is there anything else
you can think of?
I only knew her as a classmate,
so I don't really know.
11 over 14 is square root of 3.
In my 20 years of teaching,
I've seen four suicides.
It's the same every time.
It always causes a stir.
Give it six months. This
will be completely forgotten.
Only those that gab and
make a fuss will fall behind.
You get exactly
what you put into it.
Memorizing one more
english expression and
solving one more math
problem is what you should do.
Ma'am, they want Young Hee next.
It's not true, is it?
What?
Kids say you infect others
with bad thoughts.
You're here. Please sit here.
Okay. What's your name?
Lee Young Hee.
Right. Lee Young Hee.
Grade 2 Class 7.
You must know why I asked to see you.
Your memory can help us understand
more about Kyung Min's disappearance.
It's upsetting, but please
tell me as detailed as possible
the account of what
happened yesterday. Okay?
Okay.
Good. So were you two close?
We were close until last year,
but we haven't been that close since.
I ran into her when I was buying
lipstick in front of Cheongsol Academy.
I see. Girls your age are
interested in makeup, right?
Did you see her there before?
No.
I see.
If you weren't close, how
did you end up hanging out?
I just struck up a conversation.
Just?
Yes.
Just...
She just looked bored.
It's been a while, so I said hello.
So you asked her first
if she wanted to hang out.
With Han Sol.
I was on my way to a
show with another friend,
so I asked Kyung Min if
she wanted to come with us.
Did she looked different
from her usual self?
I couldn't say that.
Did she looked lonely and distressed?
- I think so.
- I see.
Then you two came back by bus, right?
Yes.
You got off by the river,
one stop before your house.
I suggested we walk a bit.
You left Han Sol behind to
walk alone with Kyung Min?
Han Sol didn't want to walk.
Kyung Min wanted to. She said
she wanted some fresh air.
I heard you abruptly
got off with Kyung Min,
leaving Han Sol behind.
No.
No?
I heard you said you wanted
to see Kyung Min die.
That's not true.
It's not?
No.
Hi, Han Sol.
Sit here.
You tell us what happened.
What do I say?
Just speak freely.
Speak freely about what you saw.
Kyung Min
seemed to be a bit on edge.
But
I got the feeling
Young Hee was egging her on.
Did you hear that?
No, I didn't.
Kyung Min said she
had feelings for you,
and you told her to prove
it by killing herself.
You asked her if she could die.
You said you wanted to
see someone die in real life.
I didn't mean anything by that.
Young Hee, Han Sol's
being brave for Kyung Min.
I was just kidding.
We hadn't hung out in while,
but she suddenly said she love
me, so I asked if she meant it.
I said if she could
prove it with her life!
- Ma'am, please calm down!
- Prove it with her life?
- Take her outside.
Prove it with her life?
Why are you lying?
I only told them what I saw.
Didn't you go to see if
Kyung Min had really died?
Hey, hey, hey.
Go away and study.
What's the matter?
Hey, hey, hey.
Move, kids.
Ma'am, you can't get
so worked up like that.
We have to scare the kids
to get something out of them.
Geez.
I'll try to talk something
out of her, so wait here.
Han Sol, thank you. You can go.
Young Hee, let's go over this again.
Put your arms down.
Look at me.
You and Kyung Min were
somewhat close until last year
but not so much since, correct?
Yes.
Then you chanced upon
her after school yesterday.
Yes.
You approached her first?
But she seemed rather off, correct?
- Yes.
- Then...
You said something that
suggested her to commit suicide.
It just came up in the
course of our conversation.
In any case...
Explain.
I'm just saying the
mood wasn't serious.
Don't focus on yourself but think
about how she might've taken it.
Damn it.
You little punk.
Mind your manners.
Hey, twerp!
You're implying that I killed Kyung Min.
Who said that?
No one here ever said that.
Did I say that?
Did I say such a thing?
Are you feeling guilty and sorry now?
Look at me.
Don't you think something
triggered Kyung Min?
That's what I think.
She studied at cram school every day.
Why did she suddenly
go drinking and clubbing?
Why are you asking me that?
I didn't force her to come.
Then why did you leave
Han Sol behind on the bus back?
One might say you wanted
Han Sol out of the picture
so you could be alone with Kyung Min.
Han Sol was sulking.
And we were being silly.
- That's not true.
- It's not true?
Of course it's not true.
You two kissed.
It was on the CCTV.
Kyung Min fell for you,
and you fell for her too.
I understand because I was
hot-blooded too at your age.
I'm not interested in
your relationship with her.
I just want you to explain
last night's inexplicable mood.
"I'm not scared of dying."
"Isn't it a relief that one day,
all of this will be over?"
That's what Kyung Min said.
So I told her my suicide plan.
I'm jumping off that bridge too
before I turn 20 years old.
I want to die too.
I thought that would comfort her.
That'll be all.
You can go now.
What are you doing?
I said, what are you doing?
Mr. Seo said
- look in the classroom
- What the hell are you doing?
For Kyung Min's will.
Look for it.
Look for it!
(Cheongsol Academy)
What did that girl just say?
She was looking for a friend.
What are you doing around doing?
Checking.
Checking what?
Do you believe that Kyung Min's dead?
She's screwing with me right now.
She doesn't have the guts to die.
She's probably hiding
somewhere laughing...
Don't act dumb.
You knew everything.
You did this to Kyung Min.
I will find her.
I will prove you wrong.
Where is it? Damn it.
Did Kyung Min kill herself
because she liked Young Hee
but was rejected?
What are you talking about?
They did always go
to the restroom together.
I remember seeing them
holding hands inside the pocket.
Hey, where is it?
How much farther?
You said you knew.
I don't know exactly either.
Then why'd you fucking say you knew?
Hurry and remember it.
Remember where it is.
The principal apparently
asked Kyung Min's mom
to say that Kyung Min
just slipped and fell.
Why?
They're liable for a lot
of things if it's a suicide.
But it is a suicide, right?
- It is, but...
- But what?
It's obvious Lee Young Hee killed her.
Without lifting a finger,
she bewitched her with her eyes.
Hey, did you know her eyes
are different in colors?
- Really?
- Yep.
I bet she's been seeing right through you.
Stop it.
I'm hungry.
Is this the right alley?
I think this is it.
Hey, don't go in. Come out.
No.
Hey, it is...
It's so dark.
Holy crap.
Is this it, right?
- Try this.
- Hey, give it here.
This is to avenge Kyung Min, you bitch.
You can't avenge anyone.
Why not? It's fun.
I'm gonna rip it.
- It won't fucking rip.
- Hey, give me the knife.
Hey, you do this.
You do it.
Come here. Let's do it together.
Hey, sit.
Let's do it together.
- Film it.
- Hurry up.
Cut it up.
What the hell?
Bitch!
You fucking bitch!
Fuck you!
Hey, give me the knife.
Give it, you bitch!
Move!
Sorry ass bitch,
why'd you push it?
We're screwed.
Why'd you take the knife out, bitch?
Fuck. I don't know.
She won't tell on us
to Mr. Seo, will she?
What kind of trouble
are you getting into?
Stop being dramatic and go in.
Go in.
You'd better behave yourself.
Be careful!
We'll drop this to the
riverbed and do a sweep.
It's heavy, so if we go slowly
to keep it from rising,
the barbed wires will catch
clothes, skin, hair, and such.
It will be better than
groping around 20-30 cm at a time.
But it can damage the body.
We'll proceed then.
All set?
Are you ready?
Be careful.
Check as soon as
something gets caught.
This is the last time.
Stay focused and
take good care of yourself.
Take good care!
Go slowly. Slowly.
How did it warp this badly?
These crappy barbed wires.
Damn it.
It was very rocky.
The boat should've moved
at a set speed, but...
The communication was... damn.
Will that be?
Are you from marines too?
Fuck, communication is...
Hey, pick these up.
Sir, I think we should stop
the search after this week.
What are you talking about?
We haven't found her.
There's a lot of pressure
from the higher up.
We're using a lot of manpower here.
Many investigations have been
suspended because of this.
Anyway, bodies are bound
to rise to the surface in time.
Do you guarantee that?
But why haven't you found her yet?
We find it regrettable too.
Don't apologize.
Just do your job.
Ma'am, you're out of line.
- What are you doing?
- Have we been twiddling our thumbs?
What are you doing, shithead?
Watch it.
I'm sorry.
Out!
I'm sorry, ma'am.
He's an emotional fellow
and slipped up. I'm sorry.
Ma'am, please calm down.
Come this way.
Sir, I'm sorry.
Come over here...
We did our best, but alas...
I know how hard you've
been working on this.
She slipped up too because
she's so distraught.
I have a kid too, so I
don't know what to say.
But can't you help us a bit more?
That's not up to us.
- Do you smoke?
- I'm okay.
The case will probably close
as impulsive suicide.
Kyung Min probably wanted
some things left alone.
It doesn't seem respectful of her
to try to dig too deep.
The detective said earlier that
it would make sense
if she has lost her footing.
If the police conclude that way,
the insurance company
will help us better.
For an insurance claim,
loss of footing is
more advantageous than suicide.
What?
It might be better for us that...
Kyung Min's body is missing.
Let's think she's alive somewhere.
From now on, all we have to do is...
Getting out of this torment.
You must be insane.
Do you want to conclude by saying
that she accidently fell and died?
Nothing will be changed.
She won't come back!
It's done!
If we don't pull ourselves
together, everything will collapse.
We need to know at
least why she died.
We have to know why she's
been thinking that way!
If we do that, we just let Kyung Min
go without truly understanding her.
You should've taken care of her!
A person called mother is
only crazy about her own work...
What the hell?
Then what did you
do as a father? Huh?
Did you do anything for her?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Breathe deeply.
Breathe!
Breathe...
Are you alright?
Honey...
Lower it.
Move it, will you?
It's slippery.
Hey, hold that side
right so it doesn't slip.
Easy.
Okay. So who's at the center?
Kyung Min, right?
And who's on the right?
Kyung Min's family.
You'll enter in groups of six.
Each group will have a representative.
The representative lays a flower here,
placing the stem toward Kyung Min.
You'd normally light an incense too
but you won't, in case you start a fire.
Then step back, stand in a line,
and bow. Twice.
Then you'll bow to the family, okay?
There are always idiots
who say hello or how are you.
- You're here.
- Mr. Seo.
- Yes!
Kyung Min's grandmother
wanted a send-off rite for her.
There's our class.
Five representatives per class
and five representatives
per grade are participating.
You can come down.
The family members haven't
slept and are in distraught so...
Who's laying the flower?
I am.
Yes. The group representative.
Remember what I've told you?
Keep the kids together
so they don't scatter, okay?
There's no representative here?
- It's me.
- You?
Sir, come on down.
Why didn't you raise your hand?
- I did.
- Stay focused.
There's that suicide
prevention training.
Yes.
Let's do that again.
Yes, sir.
We'll schedule it soon.
Okay.
This way.
My sweet girl.
Mom, should I get Hye Suk?
Leave her be. She's exhausted.
Let's talk after I go in and see.
Okay.
I can still see her.
When she came home from school,
she looked for me.
She looked for me.
I can still see her.
Stand here.
- I'm so sorry.
- Thank you for coming.
Be respectful, okay?
Kyung Min. Kyung Min.
My Kyung Min.
My poor dear Kyung Min.
My sweet girl.
Kyung Min.
My poor dear Kyung Min.
Good heavens, my sweet girl.
The students seem to be
respectful and orderly.
Yes, we have good kids at our school.
We gave them instructions beforehand.
Oh, you came too.
I have something to tell you.
What happened to your face?
I want to revise my statement a bit.
What?
Just a few lines.
I remembered something.
Everyone should know
exactly what happened.
Okay. I get what you mean.
You can come see me later.
Mr. Seo.
Mr. Seo, it won't take long.
I did some thinking.
What?
Kyung Min.
She was going to die anyway.
I remembered the last thing
she said that night.
She definitely told me that
she'd been thinking of dying
even before she ran into me.
Young Hee.
I've been feeling really bad and guilty.
But I've had no reason to.
She was going to take sleeping
pills and die that night.
She said she had her
mom's sleeping pills,
which she had collected by
lifting one or two at a time.
So I told her the success
rate was very low with those.
She would've killed herself with
those if she hadn't run into me.
I get what you're saying
and will take it into account.
Let's call it a day.
Mr. Seo, let's stop.
Yes, Young Hee. Let's stop here.
No one thinks it's your fault.
But I still want to
accurately revise my statement
so that everyone knows.
Everyone already knows.
And we only used your statement
as reference. So enough.
Young Hee, you need to know this.
What you're doing right now
is an awful thing to do
to Kyung Min. You know that?
Everyone here is deeply upset.
We're all upset.
You're being selfish right now.
You little twerp.
- Calm down.
- You little twerp.
Just look at her attitude.
It happens. She's still a kid.
That's enough.
But still...
I should have died first.
What?
I was thinking of killing myself first.
I did long thought of
jumping off that bridge,
but she stole my idea.
Are you threatening me right now?
That's no way to speak
to your teacher. Enough!
Say it again. What did you say?
Don't you know the adults
have been looking out for you?
I really did think of
killing myself first.
You little jerk.
She was your friend!
You've picked up nothing
but nasty crap. Little squirt.
I'm leaving.
When my spirit rises,
Mom...
Mom... It's me, Kyung Min.
Mom... Mom, I'm sorry.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, mom.
I'm sorry.
Yes. Go to a better place.
Hey, she's crazy.
She kept her eyes open even
when she was puking blood.
Wow. That's insane.
So she was forcing herself
to keep her eyes open?
Despite the foaming of her mouth,
she glared at each of us.
Like she was possessed
and cursing people.
So creepy.
Young Hee's conscious.
Bullshit.
Who told you?
You wouldn't say that
if you'd seen her.
She was throwing up blood
and shaking all over.
She's perfectly fine and walking.
Really?
So she's fully recovered?
Yeah.
She probably never wanted to die.
She might've put on an act to earn
sympathy after killing Kyung Min.
You all think she killed Kyung Min.
Excuse me.
Did Young Hee really wake up?
It's my wishful thinking.
I'd like her to live.
Don't read it.
Give it to your parents.
I really hope you guys
will all get along now.
Thankfully, Young Hee's
gotten better.
So those of you who can,
let's go visit her.
Class representative,
find out how many can go. Okay?
That's about it.
Young Hee says she was so
upset by Kyung Min's death.
She's also very sorry for
doing something so foolish.
Those of you who feel bad
about something you've done
to Young Hee, visit her
as a form of apology.
Class adjourned.
Thank you, Mr. Seo.
You said Young Hee
told you everything.
You said she called you that night
and said Kyung Min might die.
You said Young Hee made
Kyung Min to do it!
You lied, didn't you?
Crazy bitches.
- I'm tired
- I blew so many.
Hurry up and blow.
Mr. Seo, these are fresh flowers.
Match the color.
This one fits better.
Keep it down.
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
Please keep it down. Go on in.
Yes, ma'am. I can hear you.
Yes. It's ward 9.
The number 9.
You are there already.
If you walk into...
Wait a second, ma'am.
Hello, sir.
I was about to pick you up...
We'll all get the axe
if she doesn't wake up.
I can't take it anymore
whatever happens in school.
- Got it?
- Yes, sir.
Tell the other teachers too.
One strike and you're out.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
I'll keep that in mind.
There she is.
Hello.
Shall we go in?
Lift!
The inside's all damaged.
We made an incision in
the front to insert a tube.
She will have a hard time
eating or speaking for a while,
but it could've been a lot worse.
She ruined your daughter's wake.
I will get solace from
seeing Young Hee do well.
I'll visit often.
We wouldn't be comfortable with that.
I think I have the right.
You know that Young Hee's surgery
was paid for in small part
by the school foundation,
and the remainder was with
Kyung Min's insurance payout.
Going down.
Hang in there.
Everyone misses you.
Geez, Min Young. Speak up.
I was going to.
With a smile.
But didn't she said a lot
of shit about Young Hee?
I know. Why's she going overboard?
Ready?
Yes. That can go inside.
Just leave that.
Oh. We'll take that last.
Ah, I found this.
It was lying around so I took it.
You won't find it if it's
mixed with everything else.
How are you?
Look at this.
Fighting!
Everyone misses you.
They found Kyung Min's will.
It doesn't say why she killed herself.
She just apologized to
some classmates and her mom.
Which classmates?
Just kids she was close to.
Heard she mentioned
you too, apologizing.
Five.
Eight.
I can't see.
She used to come to me for advice.
But I lashed out at her once
because I was in a bad mood.
That was nagging at me,
but she said she forgave me
as we're very good friends.
Young Hee said Kyung Min
really hated someone,
but she can't remember who.
Where is the root?
Tree...
Are you still having nightmares?
Kyung Min...
With you...
Play?
Okay.
Then you realize it was just a dream?
And when you see Kyung Min again...
Hello.
It's been a while,
Young Hee. How are you?
You need to get better soon.
You should've called first.
It won't be long.
Consider it a present from Kyung Min.
Never forget Kyung Min.
You should go. Please.
I just want to give her this.
- Please go.
- I just want to give her this.
Stop harassing her.
The world knows my daughter
had nothing to do with it.
It's been concluded.
What's been solved?
What's been concluded?
When she's standing there
with her lips sealed?
There's something you
haven't told me, isn't it?
I can't take this anymore.
- Young Hee.
- Just go!
- You need to leave now. Please!
Young Hee! What's wrong?
Young Hee, calm down. It's okay.
Why are you angry at my daughter
over your daughter's death?
Young Hee, it's okay.
Calm down, okay?
Exhale.
Inhale.
More.
Exhale. Good job.
One more time.
Inhale.
That night,
Kyung Min and I fought
when you weren't around.
Don't try to win Young Hee
over with such lies.
You can't kill yourself.
You'll see tomorrow.
You'll see whether I'm lying or not.
"You'll see tomorrow."
"You'll see whether I'm lying or not."
I still hear her
saying that sometimes.
I can still see her eyes.
Forgive me.
I sat back and let this happen.
I played dumb.
I really liked you.
You left me alone.
I raised my head
What do you see?
I shook my head
I don't see anything
It's dark, dark, dark
I'm beautiful
You're beautiful too
It's uncomfortable at first,
but you'll get used to it.
Young Hee, I'm sorry.
This means to cheer up.
I heard you're learning sign language.
I'll have to work hard
to converse with you.
Everyone make mistakes in life.
Because we're imperfect.
Despite that, we must carry on.
How do we do that?
We must quickly forget.
At times like this,
you have to be thick-skinned.
Your long awaited friend
has returned today.
Holy shit.
Was that your seat, Young Hee?
Go sit.
Okay.
I am here
to complete my death,
for which all of you
have always wanted.
In front of all of you,
I want to die
a wonderful death.
Go sit.
Although Young Hee's much better now,
we must be mindful so
she doesn't get stressed.
Should I do your class duty next week?
Oh, come on.
I'll fetch you your lunch then.
Then I'll buy you snacks.
"Don't give in even if you're
dealt with a hundred blows."
This Chinese proverb tells us
despite many trials and
tribulations, we must unite and...
We ran out of time so you
couldn't sing last time, right?
Yes, I was disappointed.
Then should we go do karaoke later?
Shall we?
You need to unwind.
Let's do karaoke.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Ms. Park. Come sit here.
I'm very sorry.
I was so frazzled that I forgot
about this PTA gathering.
Let me pour you a drink.
Thank you.
We suspected you
because of this bitch.
You said Kyung Min
cursed her to the end.
I didn't!
She went around saying she
wanted Kyung Min to die.
I'm sorry!
I didn't know things
would turn out this way.
I'm sorry.
- Isn't this pretty?
- Yeah.
Isn't it 'carress'?
It's 'caress'.
Is it 'carress' or 'caress'?
- Isn't it 'caress' with one 'r'?
- Right?
Is it 'wrapped his arm around'
or 'wrapped his arm round'?
I think it's 'around'.
Yeah, it's 'around'.
You're good at sports, flexible,
and have a nice figure.
He said, as he caressed my thigh
and wrapped his arm around my waist.
You're great, but your flaw
is that you're young.
He caressed my thigh and
wrapped his arm around my waist.
I wonder if this is appropriate
for a teacher to do to a student.
I wouldn't feel this wronged
if I really did all of these.
Would you like to caress them now?
Mr. Seo, the detectives
are here about Da Som
so we came to get you.
Let's focus.
I didn't catch that.
Mei ting jian le
Again.
About the scholarship...
We're very grateful.
But some of students'
mothers are against it.
An anonymous donation
to the foundation is fine,
but a scholarship in your
daughter's name is a bit...
Why?
Is it wrong of one
classmate to help others?
You know how it is.
The kids and teachers
need some time to heal.
Kyung Min was a student
at this school too.
We're heartbroken too.
You're a decent person.
We're trying our best for
Kyung Min to be remembered
by the students as a good friend.
You look good.
I'm relieved because
I'd been worried about you.
We're here to see Ms. Park Hye Suk.
General manager Park Hye Suk?
Yes. I trust you've been well.
I'm calling because your
daughter's here to see you.
But she doesn't seem
to know you resigned.
Should I put some music on?
What do you like?
We're fine.
They said my daughter came,
so I thought it was Kyung Min.
You've gotten prettier
since I last saw you.
Young Hee's doing
very well these days.
She has more friends
than she used to.
We're going to study hard
and go to a good college.
I tell myself that
Kyung Min's studying abroad.
It's more bearable that way.
We came to talk to you
because we want to move on.
We think we must tell you
what happened to get closure.
Have you girls eaten?
What about Young Hee?
Can she eat?
She can have simple things.
Every time we passed by,
Kyung Min said we should try this place.
Only now, I am here.
You want to know
what she said that night, don't you?
Kyung Min said...
No one would care if she died.
Let's just remember the good.
That's probably what
Kyung Min would want too.
But Kyung Min...
wasn't all good like you think she was.
She could be rather selfish.
That's why some times, she had
no consideration for others.
You shouldn't say that.
You two owe her.
Your life was spared
with Kyung Min's help.
You should be grateful.
It was...
my fault.
That night,
Kyung Min told me everything.
I could relate wholeheartedly
so I couldn't stop her.
I was the only one who
could have stopped her.
I should have stopped her.
I can tell after dying once.
By tomorrow,
people will ask you
why I died.
Just be sure to tell them why.
Ms. Park! Put it down!
Help!
[Improved subs by @pyururuh]